ezeeclassifiedads.com 2013-05-20

# India

This Privacy Policy lists practices of Ezee Classifieds in realtion to the compilation, utilization and disclosure of personal information in relation with [**www.ezeeclassifiedads.com**](http://www.ezeeclassifiedads.com/) (the Site). This Privacy Policy may be revised by us at any point of time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Additionally this Privacy Statement may be enhanced or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information pertaining to an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information about a group in condensed form.

### Collection of Personal Information

The Site’s registration form needs users to give us their contact information (such as full name and email address) and demographic information (such as postal code, age, etc.) and other information that will be used by us to provide better services, but users can also visit the site anonymously.

The Site uses an ad form for customers to put their ads online. The Site will collect contact information furnished voluntarily by customers to be published either online or in print, as required, and in relation with items that are offered for sale by them. We do not have the control or the regulatory authority on who views ads.

We collect and compile customers’ financial information (like account/credit card numbers etc.) to charge the user for products and services, but maintain this information only as essential to process the deal and for as long it may be mandatory by law.

Our online surveys may request visitors for their contact information (such as email addresses etc.) and demographic details (like postal code, age, income etc). We utilize the contact data obtained from our surveys to send our users information relating to our products and services. In that case Users may choose to not receive mailings from Ezee Classified Ads.

### Using Personal Information

We also use the user contact information from the registration form to send user information that the user has asked for concerning the Site or concerning services offered by us.

Profile and demographic data is also collected by the Site and this data can also be used to personalize the user’s experience on the Site, showing the user material that we think he or she would be interested in and displaying the material according to the user’s choices.

Contact information which is provided by the users may be used to contact them when required.

We use third-party advertising companies like google to deliver ads when you visit our website. These companies may use the information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements relating to goods and services which may interest you.

We may use/share user information for other purposes which may be recognized at or prior to the time that the information is collected. We also use information from users for accounting and transaction completion reasons.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

**We may divulge certain personal information in the following conditions/circumstances:**

  * to law enforcement bodies for investigating frauds or other offences
  * to financial, legal and other professional counsel
  * by publishing ads online and/or in print, as the situation may be, relating to items that are for sale by users
  * by having your mobile phone number filed on www.ezeeclassifiedads.com, you consent to receive SMS from other users who may want to contact you from the site.
  * to third party service providers and to affiliated bodies who carry out activities on our behalf,

We will not use/divulge any personal information for reasons other than those for which it was obtained, except with the approval of the individual or as necessary or acceptable by law.

### Cookies and IP Addresses

We use cookies to collect information such as browser type & operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, understanding how visitors utilize the Site. This information is vital in helping us to deliver content specific to users’ interests and to save their password so they don’t have to re-enter it every time they visit the Site. 

We use cookies to collect information such as browser type & operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, understanding how visitors utilize the Site. This information is vital in helping us to deliver content specific to users’ interests and to save their password so they don’t have to re-enter it every time they visit the Site. The Site uses other ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may also contain cookies. While we use cookies in other applicable parts of the Site, cookies that are received with banner ads are gathered by our ad companies, and we don’t have any access to this information. 

As a user you can accept or decline cookies. These days most of the web browsers accept cookies, but you as a user can alter your browser setting to not accept cookies if you prefer, though this may constrict you from taking the maximum advantage of the Site. 

The site can use IP addresses of users to recognize them and their membership, collect a broad range of demographic information about users, identify problems with our server, and administer the Site.

**Log Files**

Like most websites, this Site uses log files which include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, type of platform, date/time stamp, number of clicks to study trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate and to collect broad demographic information for use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**

This Site has links to other websites like websites providing nationwide search capabilities and information resources which are designed to notify buyers and sellers about general aspects of the property that is being sold. However, once the users have used these links to leave our site, they should note that we do not have any power over that other website so we are not responsible for the safety and privacy of any information which users provide while visiting such sites and those sites are not governed by this privacy statement. So users should be careful and should look at the privacy statement of the website in question.

**Security**

The Site is ensures that users’ personally identifiable information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, the site has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect and secure the information we collect online. Only approved employees, agents and third parties have access to this information. All the emails and newsletters from this site allow users to opt out of further mailings. We dedicatedly safeguard users against the loss, alteration or misuse of personal information with ncessary security measures as needed to the sensitivity of the information, but it is likely that any information transmitted over the Internet may also be intercepted by unknown individuals/parties.

**Opt-Out**

When fit users of the Site are given the chance to (i) opt-out of getting communications from us, (ii) choose to no longer accept services from us, or (iii) eliminate their information from our database. If users choose to opt-out of receiving any further communications they can contact the Site.

**Corrections/Modifications/Contact**

Users of the Site can contact Ezee Classified Ads to correct/modify any of their personal information which is under the Site’s control. Users may also send a complaint in writing regarding compliance with this particular Privacy Statement to us and inside an appropriate time upon receiving the written complaint, we will carry out an analysis into the issue, and will take essential steps to fix the cause of the complaint.

**Contact us**

If users have any questions about this particular Privacy Statement or our privacy practices in relation to the site with this Site, or our compilation, use, disclosure, or custody of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact us at [**_info@ezeeClassifiedAds.com._**](mailto:info@ezeeClassifiedAds.com)
